(Jimmy:)What apology?
(Leonard:)For all the crappy stuff you did to me
in high school.
Oh, jeez, you're still harping on that?
What a puss.
- That's my French toast.
- It's good.
(Jimmy:)You really know your way
around a kitchen, Nancy.
(Sheldon:)I'm not going to say I told you so,
but we could've killed him.
(Leonard:)I might kill him right now.
(Sheldon:)The Dark Knight has your back.
(Sheldon:)He's scared, but he has your back.
Hey, Jimmy, it's time for you to go.
- Yeah, let me just finish this.
- No. You're done.
- I want you out of my apartment now.
- Well said, Boy Wonder.
(Jimmy:)Or what?
Don't answer. That's a trick question.
I speak from experience.
I'm not afraid of you anymore, Jimmy.
(Leonard:)Now, get out.
(Leonard:)Uh-oh.
(Sheldon:)You did it.
You stood up to your bully.